{
    "id": "7accd7ae563141eb8958030245172360",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was a …………………………… group of rich and poor, old and young.",
            "description": "Heterogeneous means mixed or diverse.",
            "answers": [
                "heterogeneous",
                "heterogenous",
                "heterogenuous"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Prices have never been so ……………………………",
            "description": "High can be an adjective and an adverb. Highly means very much.",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………….. impressed by her performance.",
            "description": "Highly means very much.",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Lack of education could be a …………………………… to your career.",
            "description": "Hindrance means obstacle.",
            "answers": [
                "hinderance",
                "hindrance",
                "hindred"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… I will take your advice.",
            "description": "Both expressions mean from now on.",
            "answers": [
                "Hereafter",
                "Henceforth",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t make important decisions ………………………………",
            "description": "Hastily means quickly or speedily.",
            "answers": [
                "haste",
                "hastily",
                "hastly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There was ……………………………… a foot of water in the well.",
            "description": "Hardly means scarcely or barely.",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The Sundarbans are the …………………………. of the Royal Bengal Tiger.",
            "description": "Habitat means natural home.",
            "answers": [
                "habitat",
                "habitants",
                "habitation"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "These huts are not fit for …………………………..",
            "description": "Habitation means occupancy.",
            "answers": [
                "habitat",
                "habitation",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The youth was so …………………………. he bought the Eiffel Tower from a con man.",
            "description": "Gullible means easily fooled.",
            "answers": [
                "guile",
                "gullible",
                "culpable"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Your accusation must be …………………………. on facts.",
            "description": "Grounded is the past tense of ground.",
            "answers": [
                "grinded",
                "ground",
                "grounded"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His …………………………… insult angered me.",
            "description": "Gratuitous means uncalled for.",
            "answers": [
                "gratuitous",
                "gracious",
                "graceful"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}